sup everyone chambers what is he four
five you with a very special video now
let me tell you this what I got
in store for you today where it's the
good
now I something you may only know if you
follow me on Twitter recently I bought
the Sonia and Knuckles puzzle as you can
see give y'all here all the boxes pretty
cool and bitchin if you ask me
now now here's what here's what
comes in a few minutes ago I was
actually working on the review for my
Sonia and Nakhla puzzles when the
mailman came to the doing
and he had dropped off another package
now being me I I do my research
now my mama I told her ass mama buy me a
Sonic calls to go to my Sonia
Knox puzzle or somebody's getting her
ass beat so let's just say I went you
into insurgency and tired that somebody
bought me a Sox puzzle for Christmas and
what do you know my mom my mama she is
away from work right she the way I work
right now and
so let's just say she's not here to stop
me from opening this I mean I know she's
waiting for waiting for Christmas to
give it to me but I don't give a so
so how about we just say let's rip this
open now now I I went a Manic one
existent ship and apparently it doesn't
turn says Sonia and knock with which
which up guy right now and and the
Robotnik kill but I don't give a
about him now now just now in
case my mama sees this cuz she watching
my videos mama
you brought you brought this on yourself
like you bought me this present you
thought you left
you went to work knowing that this is a
yeah I mean you in the ass
oh look at look at that everyone Sonic
the Hedgehog is in the house let's do
this mama mama
check his feet that what the
dancing there's another Sonia
puzzle look at that see cuz this is the
one I bought like two weeks ago what the
I told my mama I told her I wanted
the Sonic puzzle why'd she buy
me another Sonia one ah what am I gonna
do with you Sonja are you
kidding me God down
shut down well I don't need another song
you want merry Christmas to me I guess I
mean I mean now what the
why did my mama gave me and Sonia well I
suppose he asked for Sonia a Hedgehog
what sorry I supposed to be asked but
Sonic the Hedgehog why she gave me
another Sonia one what the
I don't need another Sonia one I don't I
don't need it I don't need it
what's the fun I don't need it God
you down mama watch bunny
I want it's all a job my
collection is gonna be all this all now
people be looking at my classes in wine
you ask you some young with a sudden
I don't know my mama she actually
bought me a Sonja bubble Christmas what
the